[
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:05:49.303879",
    "type": "pause_question",
    "run_number": 1,
    "scenario": 1,
    "condition": 0,
    "pause_point": 1,
    "question": "Has more than one package been discovered?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:06:52.194064",
    "type": "pause_question",
    "run_number": 1,
    "scenario": 1,
    "condition": 0,
    "pause_point": 2,
    "question": "Which quadrant has most packages been discovered?",
    "answer": "NE"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:08:46.176055",
    "type": "pause_question",
    "run_number": 1,
    "scenario": 1,
    "condition": 0,
    "pause_point": 3,
    "question": "Which containment zone will robot 3 deliver its package to?",
    "answer": "b. Robot 3 will remain in the SW quadrant and deliver its package in the SW"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:09:01.999480",
    "type": "post_scenario",
    "segment_start_time": "2025-11-09T01:08:46.176065",
    "run_number": 1,
    "scenario": 1,
    "condition": 0,
    "view_type": "map",
    "framework": "with_framework",
    "answers": {
      "mental_demand": "4 - High",
      "physical_demand": "4 - High",
      "temporal_demand": "4 - High",
      "performance": "2 - Poor",
      "effort": "1 - Very Low",
      "frustration": "3 - Moderate"
    }
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:10:03.834216",
    "type": "pause_question",
    "run_number": 2,
    "scenario": 2,
    "condition": 3,
    "pause_point": 1,
    "question": "Which robot(s) are currently navigating around an obstacle?",
    "answer": "Robot 2"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:11:13.930623",
    "type": "pause_question",
    "run_number": 2,
    "scenario": 2,
    "condition": 3,
    "pause_point": 2,
    "question": "What obstacle is Robot 3 facing?",
    "answer": "Robot 3 is stuck in rough terrain"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:14:57.510863",
    "type": "pause_question",
    "run_number": 2,
    "scenario": 2,
    "condition": 3,
    "pause_point": 3,
    "question": "Which robot do you expect will finish its task last?",
    "answer": "Robot 2"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:15:33.062586",
    "type": "post_scenario",
    "segment_start_time": "2025-11-09T01:14:57.510873",
    "run_number": 2,
    "scenario": 2,
    "condition": 3,
    "view_type": "text",
    "framework": "without_framework",
    "answers": {
      "mental_demand": "3 - Moderate",
      "physical_demand": "2 - Low",
      "temporal_demand": "3 - Moderate",
      "performance": "3 - Moderate",
      "effort": "4 - High",
      "frustration": "4D - High"
    }
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:18:31.060579",
    "type": "pause_question",
    "run_number": 3,
    "scenario": 3,
    "condition": 2,
    "pause_point": 1,
    "question": "What is the status of Robot 2?",
    "answer": "Replanning due to rough terrain"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:19:48.996124",
    "type": "pause_question",
    "run_number": 3,
    "scenario": 3,
    "condition": 2,
    "pause_point": 2,
    "question": "What are the implications of robot 2 being caught in a bad weather system?",
    "answer": "Robot 2 will desert its mission entirely"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:22:28.201172",
    "type": "pause_question",
    "run_number": 3,
    "scenario": 3,
    "condition": 2,
    "pause_point": 3,
    "question": "Which robot is likely to deliver a package next?",
    "answer": "Robot 3"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:23:51.722225",
    "type": "post_scenario",
    "segment_start_time": "2025-11-09T01:22:28.201183",
    "run_number": 3,
    "scenario": 3,
    "condition": 2,
    "view_type": "text",
    "framework": "with_framework",
    "answers": {
      "mental_demand": "5 - Very High",
      "physical_demand": "5 - Very High",
      "temporal_demand": "5 - Very High",
      "performance": "4 - Good",
      "effort": "4 - High",
      "frustration": "4D - High"
    }
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:24:25.244936",
    "type": "pause_question",
    "run_number": 4,
    "scenario": 4,
    "condition": 1,
    "pause_point": 1,
    "question": "Which quadrant is Robot 3 in?",
    "answer": "NW"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:25:59.792262",
    "type": "pause_question",
    "run_number": 4,
    "scenario": 4,
    "condition": 1,
    "pause_point": 2,
    "question": "Why is Robot 3 in the NW quadrant?",
    "answer": "Robot 1 requested Robot 3 to pick-up a package in the NW region"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:29:53.392648",
    "type": "pause_question",
    "run_number": 4,
    "scenario": 4,
    "condition": 1,
    "pause_point": 3,
    "question": "Which containment zone will robot 3 end its mission?",
    "answer": "NE"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:31:17.495411",
    "type": "post_scenario",
    "segment_start_time": "2025-11-09T01:29:53.392676",
    "run_number": 4,
    "scenario": 4,
    "condition": 1,
    "view_type": "map",
    "framework": "without_framework",
    "answers": {
      "mental_demand": "4 - High",
      "physical_demand": "4 - High",
      "temporal_demand": "4 - High",
      "performance": "4 - Good",
      "effort": "4 - High",
      "frustration": "4D - High"
    }
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-11-09T01:31:17.512557",
    "type": "post_study",
    "answers": {
      "effectiveness": null,
      "effectiveness_detail": null,
      "replan_clarity": null,
      "confusion_detail": null,
      "final_feedback": null
    }
  }
]